Register of the Robert Daniel Murphy papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Later Years I, 1959-1978 (Boxes 93-143)
  - Correspondence
    - General
      - 1967 (Folder 8-9)
      - 1968 (Folder 10-15)
      - including correspondence of the Presidential Transition Committee, 1968 (Box 94, Folder 1-15)
      - including correspondence of the Presidential Transition Committee, 1969 (Box 95, Folder 1-9)
      - including correspondence of the Presidential Transition Committee (Folder 6 WITHDRAWN. SECURITY CLASSIFIED MATERIAL), 1969 (Box 96, Folder 1-7)
      - 1970 (Folder 8-9)
      - 1970 (Box 97, Folder 1-4)
      - 1971 (Folder 5-8)
      - 1971 (Box 98, Folder 1-4)
      - 1972 (Folder 5-11)
      - 1973 (Box 99, Folder 1-12)
      - 1974 (Box 100, Folder 1-5)
      - 1975 (Folder 6-9)
      - 1976 (Folder 10-12)
      - 1976 (Box 101, Folder 1-6)
      - 1977 (Folder 7-10)
    - Abbey, Philip, 1974-1975 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Abel, Elie, 1975 (Folder 2)
    - Abrams, Creighton W., 1974 (Folder 3)
    - Abshire, David, 1970-1976 (Folder 4)
    - Acheson, Dean, 1968-1969 (Folder 5)
    - Acheson, Alice, 1971 (Folder 6)
    - Achilles, Theodore, 1974-1975 (Folder 7)
    - Adams, Charles F., 1977 (Folder 8)
    - Adenauer, Konrad, 1964 (Folder 9)
    - African American Institute, 1970 (Folder 10)
    - Agnew, Spiro, 1969 (Folder 11)
    - Aldrich, Winthrop W., 1968-1972 (Folder 12)
    - Alfalfa Club, 1970-1975 (Folder 13)
    - Alibi Club, 1972-1975 (Folder 14)
    - All-Language Services, 1975 (Folder 15)
    - Allavena, Paul, 1968 (Folder 16)
    - Allen, George V., 1968 (Folder 17)
    - Allen, Richard V., 1969 (Folder 18)
    - Alsop, Stewart, 1973 (Folder 19)
    - Altschul, Frank, 1974 (Folder 20)
    - Alverson, Lyle T., 1970-1976 (Folder 21)
    - Ambach, Dwight R., 1975 (Folder 22)
    - American Australian Association, 1970-1971 (Folder 23)
    - American Bureau for Medical Aid to China, 1977 (Folder 24)
    - American Club of Paris, 1976 (Folder 25)
    - American Committee for Assistance to Tunisia, 1973 (Folder 26)
    - American Council on Germany, 1972-1977 (Folder 27-28)
    - American Federation of Television and Radio Artists, 1969 (Folder 29)
    - American Foreign Service Association, 1967-1971 (Folder 30)
    - American Foreign Service Journal, 1969 (Folder 31)
    - American Heritage Publishing Company, 1968 (Folder 32)
    - American Hospital in Paris, 1977 (Folder 33)
    - American Irish Historical Society, 1976 (Folder 34)
    - American Korean Foundation, 1972-1976 (Box 103, Folder 1-2)
    - American Portuguese Society, 1975 (Folder 3)
    - American Research Hospital in Poland, 1965-1966 (Folder 4)
    - Anderson, George W., Jr., 1969-1975 (Folder 5)
    - Annenberg, Walter, 1970-1977 (Folder 6)
    - Arai, Yoneo, 1969 (Folder 7)
    - Areilza, Jose Ma. de, 1960 (Folder 8)
    - Armstrong, Anne, 1973-1976 (Folder 9)
    - Armstrong, Hamilton F., 1972 (Folder 10)
    - Armstrong, Willis C., 1973-1975 (Folder 11)
    - Arrow, Inc., 1972-1973 (Folder 12)
    - Asakai, Koichiro, 1963-1977 (Folder 13)
    - Asia Society, 1969-1977 (Folder 14)
    - Asian Speakers Bureau, 1969 (Folder 15)
    - Aspen Institute, 1973 (Folder 16)
    - Atlantic Council, 1976 (Folder 17)
    - Atlantic Institute, 1968 (Folder 18)
    - Avedon, Richard, 1976 (Folder 19)
    - Baeder, C. Stewart, 1969-1973 (Folder 20)
    - Baer, Elsie, 1975 (Folder 21)
    - Baker, William O., 1975 (Folder 22)
    - Ball, George W., 1967-1971 (Folder 23)
    - Barbour, P., 1976 (Folder 24)
    - Barbour, Walworth, 1975-1977 (Folder 25)
    - Barnett, A. Doak, 1971-1972 (Folder 26)
    - Barnett, Frank, 1967-1976 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Barr, Joseph, 1968-1969 (Folder 2)
    - Barrett, Edward W., 1972-1973 (Folder 3)
    - Baruch, Bernard M., Jr., 1974-1977 (Folder 4)
    - Bash, Edward J., 1972 (Folder 5)
    - Bassin, Jules, 1969 (Folder 6)
    - Battle, Lucius D., 1968 (Folder 7)
    - Battle, William C., 1969 (Folder 8)
    - Battson, Leigh M., 1970 (Folder 9)
    - Baudouin, Paul(?), 1960 (Folder 10)
    - Beal, John R., 1970-1971 (Folder 11)
    - Beam, Jacob D., 1969-1975 (Folder 12)
    - Bechtel, Stephen D., 1970 (Folder 13)
    - Beichman, Arnold, 1968-1970 (Folder 14)
    - Belgian American Chamber of Commerce, 1966-1975 (Folder 15-16)
    - Bell, Lawrence G., 1974 (Folder 17)
    - Belovsky, Sidney A., 1970 (Folder 18)
    - Bendetsen, Karl, 1973 (Folder 19)
    - Bennett, Douglas P., 1976 (Folder 20)
    - Bennett, Jack F., 1974-1975 (Folder 21)
    - Bennett, W. Tapley, Jr., 1969-1977 (Folder 22)
    - Berding, Andrew, 1973-1976 (Folder 23)
    - Berea, George de, 1976 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Berenson, Lawrence, 1967-1968 (Folder 2)
    - Bergen, John J., 1974-1978 (Folder 3)
    - Bergus, Donald C., 1973 (Folder 4)
    - Berlin, Isaiah, 1973 (Folder 5)
    - Berry, Sidney B., 1975 (Folder 6)
    - Bertrand, Henri, 1968-1975 (Folder 7)
    - Bess, Dorothy, 1966 (Folder 8)
    - Bethouart, Emile, 1975-1977 (Folder 9)
    - Bhutto, Zulfikar Ali, 1973 (Folder 10)
    - Billemon-Vernaillen, M. et Mme., 1975 (Folder 11)
    - Birrenbach, Kurt, 1971-1975 (Folder 12)
    - Bishop, Max W.S., 1970-1977 (Folder 13)
    - Black, Eugene R., 1967-1971 (Folder 14)
    - Blake, James J., 1974-1977 (Folder 15)
    - Blake, Robert, 1969-1972 (Folder 16)
    - Blomberg, W. Frary von, 1970 (Folder 17)
    - Blough, Roger M., 1971 (Folder 18)
    - Bohlen, Charles E., 1960-1971 (Folder 19)
    - Bourguiba, Habib, 1968-1976 (Folder 20)
    - Boyd, John, 1969-1977 (Folder 21)
    - Braddock, Daniel M., 1976 (Folder 22)
    - Bradley, Gene E., 1973-1974 (Folder 23)
    - Braggiotti, D. Chadwick, 1970 (Folder 24)
    - Brandt, Willy, 1969 (Folder 25)
    - Brennan, William J., Jr., 1969 (Folder 26)
    - Briggs, Ellis O., 1968-1971 (Folder 27)
    - Briley, John Marshall, 1971 (Folder 28)
    - British Broadcasting Company, 1972-1974 (Folder 29)
    - Brooks, John, 1973 (Folder 30)
    - Broomfield, William S., 1975 (Folder 31)
    - Brown, Winthrop, 1971 (Folder 32)
    - Bruce, David K.E., 1969-1976 (Folder 33)
    - Bruce, James, 1968 (Folder 34)
    - Brzezinski, Zbigniew, 1970 (Folder 35)
    - Buchanan, Wiley T., Jr., 1977 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Buckley, William F., Jr., 1967 (Folder 2)
    - Bullitt, Orville, 1970-1973 (Folder 3)
    - Bullock, Hugh, 1973-1977 (Folder 4)
    - Bundy, McGeorge, 1963 (Folder 5)
    - Burden, Mr. and Mrs. William, 1969-1975 (Folder 6)
    - Burgess, Carter, 1968-1974 (Folder 7)
    - Burgess, W. Randolph, 1970-1973 (Folder 8)
    - Burke, Arleigh, 1970-1975 (Folder 9)
    - Burke, Gerard P., 1976 (Folder 10)
    - Burke, James Wakefield, 1969 (Folder 11)
    - Burke, Lee H., 1971 (Folder 12)
    - Burns, John H., 1969-1971 (Folder 13)
    - Burns, Ward, 1970 (Folder 14)
    - Bush, Dorothy W., 1972 (Folder 15)
    - Bush, George, 1972-1976 (Folder 16)
    - Business and Industry Advisory Committee, 1970 (Folder 17)
    - Business International Corporation, 1975 (Folder 18)
    - Butrick, Richard P., 1971 (Folder 19)
    - Butterworth, Mrs. W. Walton, 1975 (Folder 20)
    - Butz, Earl L., 1971-1975 (Folder 21)
    - Cahill, Kevin, 1974 (Folder 22)
    - Calhoun, John A., 1975 (Folder 23)
    - Campbell, John F., 1970 (Folder 24)
    - Canfield, Cass, 1969 (Folder 25)
    - Capehart, Homer, 1962 (Folder 26)
    - Carey, Edwin C., 1973 (Folder 27)
    - Carey, James J., 1961 (Folder 28)
    - Carniero, Maria Cecelia Ribas, 1972 (Folder 29)
    - Carpenter, I.W., Jr., 1968 (Folder 30)
    - Carter, Jimmy, 1977 (Folder 31)
    - Carter, Marshall, 1968 (Folder 32)
    - Casey, William J., 1969-1976 (Folder 33)
    - Catudal, Honore M., Jr., 1969-1970 (Folder 34)
    - Center for Inter-American Relations, 1970-1971 (Folder 35)
    - Chambrun, Rene de, 1969-1976 (Folder 36)
    - Champion, George, 1968 (Folder 37)
    - Chancellor, John, 1973-1974 (Folder 38)
    - Chapin, Dwight, 1969 (Folder 39)
    - Chapin, Frederick, 1967 (Folder 40)
    - Chen, Thomas I., 1975-1976 (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Cherne, Leo, 1969-1977 (Folder 2)
    - Chiang Ching-kuo, 1975 (Folder 3)
    - Chiang Kai-shek, Mme. (Soong Mei-ling), 1971 (Folder 4)
    - China Institute in America, 1975 (Folder 5)
    - Chinese Information Service, 1975 (Folder 6)
    - Chow, S.K., 1973 (Folder 7)
    - Cicognani, A.G., Cardinal, 1961 (Folder 8)
    - Citadel, 1973 (Folder 9)
    - Civilian Advisory Panel on Military Manpower Procurement, 1966-1967 (Folder 10)
    - Clark, J.J., 1970-1971 (Folder 11)
    - Clark, Joan M., 1975 (Folder 12)
    - Clark, Mark W., 1967-1974 (Folder 13)
    - Clay, Lucius D., 1970-1977 (Folder 14)
    - Clemens, Cyril, 1970 (Folder 15)
    - Cleveland, Harlan, 1976 (Folder 16)
    - Clifford, Clark, 1966-1968 (Folder 17)
    - Cline, Ray S., 1976 (Folder 18)
    - Clock, Philip, 1968-1972 (Folder 19)
    - Close, Mrs. Edward B., 1975 (Folder 20)
    - Coburn, John B., 1975 (Folder 21)
    - Coffey, Mathew B., 1976 (Folder 22)
    - Colby, William E., 1975-1976 (Folder 23)
    - Columbia Broadcasting System - CBS News, 1970 (Folder 24)
    - Columbia University, 1967-1976 (Folder 25)
    - Connally, John B., 1970-1975 (Folder 26)
    - Cooke, Terence Cardinal, 1970-1977 (Folder 27)
    - Cooper, John Sherman, 1968-1973 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Cootes, Merritt N., 1972 (Folder 2)
    - Corcoran, Thomas G., 1975-1977 (Folder 3)
    - Cordier, Andrew W., 1971 (Folder 4)
    - Corning Glass Works, 1972 (Folder 5)
    - Corrigan, Robert F., 1969-1973 (Folder 6)
    - Cors, Allan, 1972 (Folder 7)
    - Cort, Stewart S., 1972 (Folder 8)
    - Coster, Donald Q., 1969 (Folder 9)
    - Council of the Americas, 1972 (Folder 10)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, 1962-1971 (Folder 11)
    - Craigie, Robert A.P., 1975 (Folder 12)
    - Cramer, Robert, 1962 (Folder 13)
    - Cronk, Edwin M., 1974 (Folder 14)
    - Cross, Cecil M.P., 1973 (Folder 15)
    - Csapski, Americ, 1969-1976 (Folder 16)
    - Csonka, Emil, 1971 (Folder 17)
    - Cummings, Nate, 1960 (Folder 18)
    - DACOR (Diplomatic and Consular Officers, Ret.), 1974 (Folder 19)
    - Dainelli, Luca, 1971-1977 (Folder 20)
    - Dana, William H., 1976 (Folder 21)
    - Davies, A. Hudson, 1968 (Folder 22)
    - Davies, Rodger P., 1973 (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Davis, Nathaniel, 1968-1972 (Folder 2)
    - Davis, Russell H., Jr., 1970-1973 (Folder 3)
    - Davis, Thomas J., III, 1975 (Folder 4)
    - Dawson, William, 1964 (Folder 5)
    - Dean, Arthur, 1970 (Folder 6)
    - DeButts, John D., 1973-1975 (Folder 7)
    - Declaration of Atlantic Unity (organization), 1967 (Folder 8)
    - Dedijer, S., 1975 (Folder 9)
    - DeFreitas, Dick, 1973 (Folder 10)
    - Dellisante, Philip, 1975 (Folder 11)
    - DeLorenzo, Anthony, 1975 (Folder 12)
    - Dennison, Charles S., 1970 (Folder 13)
    - Deutch, Michael J., 1971 (Folder 14)
    - Dewey, Thomas, 1970 (Folder 15)
    - Dickey, Charles D., 1973-1975 (Folder 16)
    - Diebold, John, 1971-1975 (Folder 17)
    - Dillon, Douglas, 1961 (Folder 18)
    - Dombroski, Theresa, 1975 (Folder 19)
    - Donaldson, John W., 1973 (Folder 20)
    - Donhauser, Robert, 1960 (Folder 21)
    - Dorange, General, 1977 (Folder 22)
    - Dorschner, John, 1977 (Folder 23)
    - Doubleday Corporation, 1971-1974 (Folder 24)
    - Douglas, Lewis W., 1971 (Folder 25)
    - Douro, Richard, 1967 (Folder 26)
    - Dressendorfer, John H., 1969 (Folder 27)
    - Ducas, John J., 1970 (Folder 28)
    - Dulles, Eleanor Lansing, 1969-1974 (Folder 29)
    - Dulles, Mrs. John Foster, 1964 (Folder 30)
    - Dunn, James Clement, 1974 (Folder 31)
    - Duranton, Roger, 1967-1971 (Folder 32)
    - Durbrow, Elbridge, 1971-1976 (Folder 33)
    - Durkee, William P., 1974-1975 (Folder 34)
    - Eagleburger, Lawrence S., 1975-1976 (Folder 35)
    - Eban, Abba, 1967 (Folder 36)
    - Eisenhower, David, 1976 (Folder 37)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1960-1961 (Folder 38)
    - Eisenhower, John, 1969-1975 (Folder 39)
    - Eisenhower, Milton, 1967 (Folder 40)
    - Elbrick, C. Burke, 1969 (Folder 41)
    - Emmerich, Franz, 1972 (Folder 42)
    - Emmet, Christopher, 1967-1973 (Folder 43)
    - Engelhard, Jane, 1975 (Folder 44)
    - Estes, Thomas S., 1968-1973 (Folder 45)
    - Fair Campaign Practices Committee, 1975 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Fairbanks, Douglas, Jr., 1967 (Folder 2)
    - Fales, Rose H., 1974 (Folder 3)
    - Far East-America Council, 1967-1975 (Folder 4)
    - Farland, Joseph S., 1969-1972 (Folder 5)
    - Farley, James A., 1963-1975 (Folder 6)
    - Fashek, Norman L., 1975 (Folder 7)
    - Ferrari, Frank, 1971 (Folder 8)
    - Figueroa, Sergio, 1972 (Folder 9)
    - Finch, Robert, 1971 (Folder 10)
    - Finn, Richard B., 1975 (Folder 11)
    - Flanigan, Peter M., 1969 (Folder 12)
    - Folger, John Clifford, 1967 (Folder 13)
    - Forbes, Malcolm S., 1974 (Folder 14)
    - Ford, Gerald, 1968 (Folder 15)
    - Ford, Henry, II, 1971 (Folder 16)
    - Ford, Thomas, 1970 (Folder 17)
    - Foreign Policy Association, 1967-1977 (Folder 18)
    - Foreign Reports, 1969-1977 (Folder 19)
    - Foreign Service Journal, 1967-1969 (Folder 20)
    - Forlani, Arnaldo, 1969-1970 (Folder 21)
    - Former Members of Congress (organization), 1977 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Fortas, Abe, 1968 (Folder 2)
    - Fowler, Henry H., 1971-1974 (Folder 3)
    - Frankel, Max, 1971 (Folder 4)
    - Franklin, William M., 1969-1975 (Folder 5)
    - Fredericks, J. Wayne, 1974-1977 (Folder 6)
    - Freedom House, 1968 (Folder 7)
    - Freeman, Orville L., 1972-1975 (Folder 8)
    - Friedrich, Harald, 1968 (Folder 9)
    - Friends of Free China, 1973-1974 (Folder 10)
    - Fukuda, Takeo, 1969-1975 (Folder 11)
    - Fulbright, J. William, 1962 (Folder 12)
    - Fullerton, Hugh Stuart, 1967-1976 (Folder 13)
    - Funk, Arthur L., 1969-1973 (Folder 14)
    - Galbo, Vincent J., 1972 (Folder 15)
    - Gallagher, Wes, 1976 (Folder 16)
    - Gallman, W.J., 1976 (Folder 17)
    - Gandilhon, J., 1968 (Folder 18)
    - Gardner, John, 1975 (Folder 19)
    - Gardner, Richard, 1973 (Folder 20)
    - Garin, Vasco Vieira, 1970 (Folder 21)
    - Garner, Robert L., 1968-1972 (Folder 22)
    - Garrett, Richard, 1971 (Folder 23)
    - Gates, Jack, 1970-1974 (Folder 24)
    - Gates, Thomas S., 1976-1977 (Folder 25)
    - Gavin, James, 1971 (Folder 26)
    - Geliot, Christian, 1967 (Folder 27)
    - George C. Marshall Research Foundation, 1968-1977 (Box 112, Folder 1-2)
    - George Washington University, 1975-1977 (Folder 3)
    - Gerhardt, H.A., 1977 (Folder 4)
    - German American Chamber of Commerce, 1972 (Folder 5)
    - Gilbert, Carl J., 1969 (Folder 6)
    - Gilchrist, Andrew and Ella, 1972 (Folder 7)
    - Gillan, T.M., 1975 (Folder 8)
    - Godley, G. McMurtrie, 1969 (Folder 9)
    - Goldberg, Arthur J., 1969 (Folder 10)
    - Goldman, Guido, 1974 (Folder 11)
    - Goldstern, Norbert, 1969 (Folder 12)
    - Goodpaster, A.J., 1968-1977 (Folder 13)
    - Gossett, Elizabeth, 1976 (Folder 14)
    - Goulli, Slaheddine el, 1972-1975 (Folder 15)
    - Gowen, Franklin C., 1975 (Folder 16)
    - Grace, J. Peter, 1973 (Folder 17)
    - Graham, Robert A., 1976-1977 (Folder 18)
    - Green, Marshall, 1971-1974 (Folder 19)
    - Greenwood, E.M., 1969-1975 (Folder 20)
    - Gromand, Roger, 1975 (Folder 21)
    - Gruson, Sydney, 1971 (Folder 22)
    - Guiringaud, L. de, 1974 (Folder 23)
    - Gutheil, Helmut, 1948-1969 (Folder 24)
    - Habib, Philip C., 1968-1976 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Hagedorn, George C., 1973-1974 (Folder 2)
    - Hahn, H.P., 1971 (Folder 3)
    - Haider, Michael, 1967 (Folder 4)
    - Haig, Alexander, (SOME ITEMS WITHDRAWN. SECURITY CLASSIFIED MATERIAL), 1970-1972 (Folder 5)
    - Haight, G.W., 1968 (Folder 6)
    - Halaby, Najeeb E., 1970-1974 (Folder 7)
    - Hall, William O., 1972 (Folder 8)
    - Halsey, James H., 1975 (Folder 9)
    - Handley, William J., 1971 (Folder 10)
    - Hanfstaengl, Egon, 1975 (Folder 11)
    - Hanser, Richard, 1976 (Folder 12)
    - Harder, Howard, 1971 (Folder 13)
    - Harlow, Bryce, 1970-1971 (Folder 14)
    - Harman, Phillip, 1975-1977 (Folder 15)
    - Harriman, W. Averell, 1963-1975 (Folder 16)
    - Harrop, William C., 1972 (Folder 17)
    - Hartley, Livingston, 1975 (Folder 18)
    - Hartwell, Samuel A., 1974 (Folder 19)
    - Hauge, Gabriel, 1971-1973 (Folder 20)
    - Hays, Brooks, 1976 (Folder 21)
    - Heath, Donald R., 1975 (Folder 22)
    - Heberle, Jean-Claude, 1971 (Folder 23)
    - Heinz, Henry II, 1975 (Folder 24)
    - Heiskell, Andrew, 1970 (Folder 25)
    - Helms, Richard, 1972-1974 (Folder 26)
    - Henrikson, Alan K., 1976 (Folder 27)
    - Henry-Haye, G., 1973-1974 (Folder 28)
    - Herter, Christian A., 1961 (Folder 29)
    - Herzog, Mrs. Yaacov, 1972 (Folder 30)
    - Hesburgh, Theodore M., 1974-1977 (Folder 31)
    - Hicks, John F.G., 1967 (Folder 32)
    - Hight, John W., 1972 (Folder 33)
    - Hill, Robert C., 1969-1973 (Folder 34)
    - Hillenbrand, Martin J., 1969 (Folder 35)
    - Hinds, A. Boyd, 1972 (Folder 36)
    - Hinton, Longstreet, 1975 (Folder 37)
    - Hoffman, Mr. and Mrs. Paul G., 1971-1974 (Folder 38)
    - Hoisington, William A., Jr., 1972 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Hoopes, Townsend, 1971-1974 (Folder 2)
    - Hoover, Mr. and Mrs. Herbert, Jr., 1967-1969 (Folder 3)
    - Hopper, Bruce C., 1967 (Folder 4)
    - Horkan, George A., 1967 (Folder 5)
    - Hottelet, Richard, 1970 (Folder 6)
    - Hotung, Eric, 1970-1973 (Folder 7)
    - Houghton, Amory, 1966-1975 (Folder 8)
    - Houghton, Arthur A., Jr., 1961-1976 (Folder 9)
    - Housman, Richard Jay, 1974 (Folder 10)
    - Howley, Frank L., 1969-1970 (Folder 11)
    - Hoxie, R. Gordon, 1973 (Folder 12)
    - Hoxter, Curtis J., 1971 (Folder 13)
    - Hrones, John, 1975 (Folder 14)
    - Hsiung, James C., 1977 (Folder 15)
    - Hughes, Thomas L., 1968-1969 (Folder 16)
    - Humes, John P., 1973 (Folder 17)
    - Humphrey, Hubert, 1967 (Folder 18)
    - Hunter, Edward, 1975 (Folder 19)
    - Ignatieff, Alex, 1974 (Folder 20)
    - Ingersoll, Robert S., 1972-1973 (Folder 21)
    - Institute of International Education, 1975-1977 (Folder 22)
    - International Executive Service Corps, 1967 (Folder 23)
    - International Management and Development Institute, 1972-1975 (Folder 24)
    - International Rescue Committee, 1969-1977 (Box 115, Folder 1-6)
    - International Telephone and Telegraph Company, 1973 (Folder 7)
    - Irvine, Reed J., 1969 (Folder 8)
    - Irwin, John, 1969-1973 (Folder 9)
    - Jackson, Henry M., 1967-1969 (Folder 10)
    - Janeway, Eliot, 1971 (Folder 11)
    - Japan America Institute, 1972 (Folder 12)
    - Japan American Cultural Society, 1975 (Folder 13)
    - Japan Fund, 1972 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Japan International Christian University Foundation, 1973-1977 (Folder 2)
    - Japan National Student Association, 1969-1975 (Folder 3)
    - Japan Society, 1969-1975 (Folder 4)
    - Johari, Gyan, 1969 (Folder 5)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1968 (Folder 6)
    - Johnson, Mrs. Lyndon B., 1968 (Folder 7)
    - Johnson, U. Alexis, 1968-1976 (Folder 8)
    - Jones, Harry W., 1976 (Folder 9)
    - Jones, James, 1970 (Folder 10)
    - Jones, Roger W., 1961 (Folder 11)
    - Jousse, General, 1973-1975 (Folder 12)
    - Judd, Walter H., 1972 (Folder 13)
    - Kaspi, Andre, 1972 (Folder 14)
    - Kearns, Henry, 1971 (Folder 15)
    - Keating, Kenneth, 1969 (Folder 16)
    - Kelly, John E., 1970 (Folder 17)
    - Kelsey, John W., Jr., 1969 (Folder 18)
    - Kennan, George, 1977 (Folder 19)
    - Kennedy, Edward M., 1977 (Folder 20)
    - Kennedy, John F., 1960 (Folder 21)
    - Kennedy, Mrs. Joseph, 1969 (Folder 22)
    - Kennedy, Robert F., 1966-1967 (Folder 23)
    - Kern, Harry F., 1968-1977 (Folder 24)
    - Kerr, Walter, 1971 (Folder 25)
    - Kessler, Frank, 1976 (Folder 26)
    - Khan, Najmul Saqib, 1972-1975 (Folder 27)
    - Kim, Young Sun, 1972 (Folder 28)
    - Kissinger, Henry, (SOME MATERIAL WITHDRAWN. SECURITY CLASSIFIED MATERIAL), 1970-1975 (Folder 29)
    - Klein, Julius, 1968-1972 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Kline, Hugh, 1975 (Folder 2)
    - Knapp, J. Burke, 1975 (Folder 3)
    - Knight, Ridgway B., 1969 (Folder 4)
    - Knoppers, Antonie T., 1975 (Folder 5)
    - Knowlton, William A., 1974 (Folder 6)
    - Knox, John, 1972 (Folder 7)
    - Knox, William, 1967 (Folder 8)
    - Koehler, John O., 1972 (Folder 9)
    - Kohler, Foy D., 1967-1976 (Folder 10)
    - Kolko, Gabriel, 1969 (Folder 11)
    - Korry, Edward M., 1975 (Folder 12)
    - Koubbi, Albert el, 1974-1977 (Folder 13)
    - Kraus, Maria, 1964-1965 (Folder 14)
    - Krock, Arthur, 1966 (Folder 15)
    - Kuhn, Irene Corbally, 1967-1975 (Folder 16)
    - Kupferman, Theodore, 1968 (Folder 17)
    - LaFollette, Charles D., 1967-1971 (Folder 18)
    - Laird, Melvin R., 1973 (Folder 19)
    - Lamont, Thomas S., undated (Folder 20)
    - Land, Edwin H., 1970 (Folder 21)
    - Langer, William, 1969 (Folder 22)
    - Lasky, Melvin J., 1971 (Folder 23)
    - Latimer, Thomas K., 1975 (Folder 24)
    - Launay, J.F. de, 1969 (Folder 25)
    - Lazrus, Oscar M., 1976 (Folder 26)
    - League of Americans Residing Abroad, 1967 (Folder 27)
    - Lehaney, Francis, 1971-1975 (Folder 28)
    - Lehmann, Manfred R., 1976 (Folder 29)
    - Lemaigre-Dubreuil, Jean-Pierre, 1974-1975 (Folder 30)
    - Lemnitzer, L.L., 1960 (Folder 31)
    - Leonard, Richard G., 1971 (Folder 32)
    - Leonhart, William, 1969-1974 (Folder 33)
    - Levy-Despas, Andre, 1961 (Folder 34)
    - Lewis, Joseph, 1975 (Folder 35)
    - Li, K.T., 1973 (Folder 36)
    - Li, Mo, 1975-1976 (Folder 37)
    - Library of Presidential Papers, 1967-1968 (Folder 38)
    - Lilienthal, David E., 1969 (Folder 39)
    - Lindsay, Franklin A., 1971 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Lindsay, John V., 1973 (Folder 2)
    - Lodge, Henry Cabot, 1958-1974 (Folder 3)
    - Lodge, John Davis, 1960-1972 (Folder 4)
    - Lodigensky, A.A., 1971 (Folder 5)
    - Loeb, John L., 1975 (Folder 6)
    - Loh, I-Cheng, 1971-1977 (Folder 7)
    - Longworth, Mrs. Nicholas, 1974 (Folder 8)
    - Loridan, Walter, 1969 (Folder 9)
    - Loughran, Jack, 1976-1977 (Folder 10)
    - Lovestone, Jay, 1967-1971 (Folder 11)
    - Lovett, Robert A., 1970 (Folder 12)
    - Lowenthal, Abraham F., 1975 (Folder 13)
    - Lubbers, Arend P., 1973-1976 (Folder 14)
    - Luce, Clare Boothe, 1975 (Folder 15)
    - Luce, Henry, III, 1973 (Folder 16)
    - Ludden, Raymond, 1969 (Folder 17)
    - Lynch, R.J., 1971 (Folder 18)
    - Lyon, Cecil B., 1967-1977 (Folder 19)
    - MacArthur, Douglas, II, 1970-1971 (Folder 20)
    - MacAvoy, Thomas C., 1975 (Folder 21)
    - Macmillan, Harold, 1967-1973 (Folder 22)
    - Macomber, William B., Jr., 1969-1971 (Folder 23)
    - Mahoney, James P., 1972 (Folder 24)
    - Maillard, William S., 1974 (Folder 25)
    - Manning, Bayliss, 1975-1977 (Folder 26)
    - Mansfield, Mike, 1976-1977 (Folder 27)
    - Marcos, Imelda, 1974 (Folder 28)
    - Marie Salvatora, Sister, 1975 (Folder 29)
    - Marquette University, 1971-1977 (Folder 30)
    - Martin, Graham A., 1968 (Folder 31)
    - Martin, William McC., Jr., 1969 (Folder 32)
    - Marwell, David G., 1977 (Folder 33)
    - Mast, Charles, 1970-1977 (Folder 34)
    - Mathias, Charles Mc., Jr., 1967-1975 (Folder 35)
    - May, Dick, 1967 (Folder 36)
    - Mayer, Charles T., 1963-1977 (Folder 37)
    - McBride, Robert, 1968-1969 (Folder 38)
    - McCarthy, Frank, 1970 (Folder 39)
    - McChrystal, Arthur J., 1976-1977 (Folder 40)
    - McClintock, Robert, 1968-1973 (Folder 41)
    - McCloy, John J., II, 1971-1977 (Folder 42)
    - McCone, John A., 1961-1971 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - McCormick, Ken, 1967-1969 (Folder 2)
    - McDowell, Robert H., 1969 (Folder 3)
    - McFall, Jack K., 1977 (Folder 4)
    - McFarland, Joseph B., 1974 (Folder 5)
    - McGhee, George C., 1965-1977 (Folder 6)
    - McGregor, Robert G., 1969 (Folder 7)
    - McIlvaine, Robinson, 1972 (Folder 8)
    - McIntyre, J.M., 1960 (Folder 9)